Guide to the Lawrence Lee Papers, 1920-1978 SC.1978.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1924-1978; II.
  - Rose, Stuart (David McKay Co. Publishers), 1963 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Rosenberger, Francis Coleman, 1974, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Scribner's, 1939-1964 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Scribner's (Burroughs Mitchell), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Sewanee Review, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Shafer, Raymond (Governor), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Tate, Allen, 1937-1953 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - University of London, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review, 1967-1975 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Watkins, Armitage ("Mike"), 1962 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Wheelock, J. to Wilson, J., 1933 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Wilson, Dr. James Southall, 1924-1958 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
  - Yale Review (J.E. Palmer), 1964 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Personal Papers, 1920-ca. 1944; III.
  Series III contains miscellaneous personal material ranging from 1920 through 1978. Includes material ranging from C.V. information to lecture notes for courses taken at Harvard and teaching notes for courses taught at the University of Pittsburgh. The series also includes a record book of Lee's distribution of author copies, materials related to Lee's home in Pittsburgh, and graduation regalia. Also includes a scrapbook containing photographs, news clippings, manuscript poems, and correspondence. Series is arranged chronologically, with undated material at the end.
  - Scrapbook pages, 1920 - circa 1944 (Box 16, Volume 1)
  - Notebook – Harvard MA coursework, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Lee's House - 510 Rosslyn Place, 1951, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Autograph Collection, 1961-1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Reading Lists for English 180 and 880, circa 1965 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Lecture Notes: European Novel, circa 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - University of Pittsburgh English Newsletter on Lee's Retirement, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dictionary of Literary Biography updates + C.V.s, 1970-1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - University of Virginia Class of 1924 50th Reunion - Thomas Jefferson Society Certificate, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - California State College Research and Service award, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Record Book - Disposal of Author Copies (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Portrait of Lee (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Program - The Fire of London by Peter Black (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - University of Pittsburgh Emeritus Certificate (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Graduation Cap, Tassle, and Hood (Box 17, Folder 14)